Finding Aid for the Kathy Sawyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Audio Cassettes
  - 6/12 Hearing I (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - RTF Workshop, September 16, 2003 (8 cassettes) (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Goldin re: X-33-34 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Goldin, March 18, 1996 (origins) (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - STSCI “Branco” dark energy fivio, Dvali etc, April 3, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Nat. Acad. Lunch and life on other planets, origins, et, May 3, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Goldin breakfast interview, May 12, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Mon am. (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - H’word, February 6, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Goldin interview, July 15, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - NASA (5 cassettes), Maran I Launch STS 63 – February 4, 1995 K-Nealson, Laurie Leshin – Mars rock – Vikins symposium – July 2001 Hoffman – water comets Goldin – Glenn flight – September 15, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Astronomy – Keck, Marcy, etc. – 1999 (6 cassettes), Marcy I – Class and Amy - February 1, 1999 Marcy Marcy 2 SETI; Dinner/ Planetarium Marcy 4 Geoff Marcy AAS (planets, publicity) f. Keck Tape II – end summit obs. (The Frozen Dome) (Box 48, Folder 32)
- Audio Cassettes
  - DIVE #1 – Alvin Dive to bottom of Pacific to study deep biosphere (Sawyer aboard) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - DIVE #2 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Atlantis I Dudley (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Atlantis II; Janet – 1026B troubles (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Maran tapes astronomy -- AAS 2001 (4 cassettes), Maran 2 Maran 3 Maran – unige AAS – 1999 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Saul V (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Saul update (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Hushes et al – JSC 11/93 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - X-33 Dennis Smith M. Albrecht (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - AASI cosmo briefing (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Readdy (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Readdy, O’Keefe – 3/14 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - O’Keefe round table, May 2003 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Bruce Murray, July 7, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Space station briefings (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Kathie Thomas – Kperta (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Final session LPI JSC/ Mars Rock 3/98 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Gore (?) (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Mars Odyssey 2001 briefing, March 19, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Mars - Nideri McLees, August 4, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Land Probe Lady, Bruce Marray, etc (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Margon November 11, 2003, HST fight (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - McCandless (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Tour (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Policy people – Weiler Mendell Thronson (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - NASP Plant visit (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Gary Martin, space arch, December 18, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Weiler, November 12, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - ASAP - soccerball universe (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Pillinger re Beagle 2 (pre landing), December 2003 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - S/D Gutierrez – 10/30 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - ISS (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - NESC, cont.; H. McCurdy space policy, December 15, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Audio Cassettes, VHS, Microcassettes
  - Audio Cassettes
    - O’Keefe interview 8/27 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - O’Keefe re: RTF, etc, October 8, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ISS Tour interview, December 3, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Space flight briefing; Elachi interview – 2/4 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Squyres, January 8 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Torrence Johnson; Europe, December 12, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Ed Weiler – Grand Challenges, March 31, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Malin re: layers on mars, 12-00 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - RTF workshop: improved management briefing, September 17, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - AAAS, February 7, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Gehman Briefing, May 6, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - VHS
    - Crier Today, February 23, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - STS88 – Mars mission preflight briefing – Skylab 25th anniversary retrospective (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Astrobiology meeting – Ames Research Center, CA – debate between Bill Schopf and Martin Brasier, April 9, 2002 (tape 1) (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Astrobiology meeting – Ames Research Center, CA – debate between Bill Schopf and Martin Brasier, April 9, 2002 (tape 2) (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Fantasy Trip to a Neutron Star – Robert J. Nemiroff (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - “Volcanoes of the Deep”, March 30, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Neil Armstrong (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Microcassette
    - March 17 – The cut-one NASA(The Guy Cohen briefing) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Bruce Morgan interview for Unige, January 18, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Shuttle launch 51-L (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - STS 26 L-O (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - John Glenn Interview – Return to Space (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Bill Schopf/Ed Weiler NASAA. McDonald, August 17, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - MBL (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Koale (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Musgrave, March 20, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Weiler – Figneroa (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Marcy (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Mars Rock (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Vali – April 2005/ ZARE Review (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Hurl (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Golden reli, March 12 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Bruce Morgan interview, January 18, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - O’Keefe, Janury 29 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Boss/Goldin (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Dan Goldin, October 25, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Re: Pathfinder (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Quayle (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - JA Pre BFC on media -- April 5, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - CD
    - Reconstruction RLV Hangar, February 2003
  - Floppy Disks
    - Climate Change Information (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Slides
    - Furthest Galaxy Discovered – 4/93 (Box 50, Folder 1)